Josephina Yergatian-Murfitt

London, United Kingdom jyergatianmurfitt@gmail.com 07519 151 665

PROFILE

A full stack software engineer with experience in JavaScript, Node.js, React, AWS products, GraphQL and SQL. I am passionate about combining my background in art with my programming skills to create clean and well-written projects. I am Interested in challenging opportunities that will broaden my skill base.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Portfolio available upon request

Mindful Education, London/UK – Junior Software Engineer

10/2021 - Present

- Using React, SQL and AWS to design and build technical solutions for a wide range of users and internal stakeholders.
- Automated continuous updating of databases for different departments using a custom script and writing unit tests to verify their functionality.
- Turning scripts into command line node applications to be used across the company.
- Reskinned the entire internal software of the company to bring it in line with our branding.
- Spinning up instances of our virtual learning environment.
- As part of a team writing a standardised style guide to unify the contents of the company's software.
- Consistently exceeded my KPIs by completing projects within required deadlines whilst adhering to feature specifications.
- Working in an Agile environment.

01/2021 - 09/2021

Taught myself JavaScript, React, HTML and CSS as well as other technologies using online resources.

Pioneers, Beirut/Lebanon - Volunteer

11/2018 - 12/2020

- I helped find sustainable solutions to the educational needs of Syrian refugee children in Lebanon.
- Taught English to Syrian refugees as part of a work reintegration programme.
- Assisted in preparing material for the Arabic literacy program run by the organisation.
- Conducted field visits to refugee homes to assess their needs and requirements.
- Helped prepare workshops for refugees including CV and soft skill building to assist them in finding work.

EDUCATION

SOAS, University of London

2015 - 2018

BA History of Art (with courses in Arabic language): 2:1

SKILLS & INTERESTS

Technical Skills: JavaScript - React - Node.js - DynamoDB - AWS - SQL - GraphQL - Apollo - Version control - Git - Bitbucket - SASS - Jest - APIs - HTML.

Languages: Fluent in English, basic proficiency in Arabic.

Hobbies: Painting, baking and running.